<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Api on Kimberly the Geek</title>
    <link>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/categories/api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Api on Kimberly the Geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 16:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/categories/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Internship: Translate Java to Python, Pt. 2</title>
      <link>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/translate-java-to-python-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/translate-java-to-python-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>Continued from Part 1
While I began writing my package as a direct, one-to-one translation of the Java package, my package turned out to look very different.
Java and Python are, after all, very different languages. I found some methods to be unnecessary in python, and chose to not use the same design pattern as axe-selenium-java.
The Java package, written by Deque Labs, uses the Builder design pattern.
I wrote the methods used by the Builder class to be methods of the Axe class instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Internship: Diving into Test Automation with Python</title>
      <link>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/test-automation-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 17:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/test-automation-python/</guid>
      <description>Test Automation with Python The first week of my internship was spent primarily setting up my dev environment on the laptop I received.
I had also never used a Mac before, so there were some basics to learn as well.
Although, since MacOS is Unix-based now, all of the important things were pretty much the same.
(I&#39;m worthless with a Windows command line)
Once I had everything configured, I started fiddling with python and pytest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AngularJS Wikipedia Search App - Part Two</title>
      <link>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/angularjs-wikipedia-search-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/angularjs-wikipedia-search-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>Continued from Part One

Build a Wikipedia Search App With AngularJS Part Two - Use Output So, if everything went as expected in the first part, you should be getting output in your console.
Now we need to actually display the output on the page.
The JavaScript We first need to modify our app so that it does something with the data besides printing to the console.
[js]
// app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AngularJS Wikipedia Search App - Part One</title>
      <link>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/angularjs-wikipedia-search-pt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/angularjs-wikipedia-search-pt-1/</guid>
      <description>Build a Wikipedia Search App With AngularJS Part One - Get Output In the previous post, I showed how to make unauthenticated API requests to the Wikipedia API.
In this tutorial, I&#39;m going to rebuild the Wikipedia Search App using AngularJS.
Here&#39;s what we&#39;re going to start with:
[js]
// app.js
(function(){
&#39;use strict&#39;;
 angular.module(&#39;wikipediaApp&#39;, [])
.constant(&#39;API_PATH&#39;, &#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/w/api.php&#39;)
.controller(&#39;SearchController&#39;, SearchController);
 SearchController.$inject = [&#39;$scope&#39;, &#39;$http&#39;, &#39;API_PATH&#39;];
function SearchController($scope, $http, API_PATH){</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the #$@&amp; Do I Use an API?! - Wikipedia API Basics</title>
      <link>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/wikipedia-api-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 15:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.kimberlythegeek.com/posts/wikipedia-api-basics/</guid>
      <description>Wikipedia API Basics 1. So... What&#39;s an API?
2. There&#39;s an API For That!
3. Okay, I Know What an API Is...Now What?
4. Let&#39;s Do It!
5. It worked! (Hopefully)


How the #$@&amp; Do I Use an API?! I&#39;m taking a break from the WordPress development topic to delve into APIs. (Yay!)
I&#39;ll be using the Wikipedia API for this example.
1. So... What&#39;s an API? APIs&amp;#8212;application programming interfaces&amp;#8212;are the current standard in utilizing information and technologies on the web.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>